Contact

hvsutton12@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/haileysutton-bsn-rn (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Team Leadership

Nursing

Adaptability

Certifications

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Registered Nurse

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

Neonatal Resuscitation Program

Honors-Awards

Deans List

Presidents List

Presidents List

Employee Of the Month

Hailey Sutton BSN, RN

New graduate nurse seeking a position in Labor and Delivery and Aesthetics.

Greater Los Angeles Area

Summary

My education includes six separate degrees for my Associates of Science at Citrus College, and a Bachelor of Science in Nursing at West Coast University, along with being recipient of Deans List award for my academic success in 2018. I feel that my previous years of care giving and becoming a supervisor has allowed for me to better understand the complexity of taking care of ill patients and complex situations. With my extensive leadership experience and many years of caring for seniors as they reach the end of life, I have learned to understand true compassion and empathy for individuals and their families in such a difficult time. Caring in such a manner has opened my eyes and has made me want to now be a part of the best part of people's lives, coming into the hospital as a woman and leaving as a mother. With my previous clinical experiences both as a care manager and as a student at West Coast University, including my preceptorship in Labor and Delivery, I have learned how to properly care and comfort a variety of patient populations during the birthing process and am eager to be able to provide warm and caring family centered care for new families.

Experience

Sunrise Senior Living
Lead care Manager
June 2016 - December 2019 (3 years 7 months)
San Gabriel, California, United States

Supported team as they provide activities of daily living to residents in accordance with Resident's Individualized Care Plan. Coordinated with care team, residents, family members, emergency personal, and internal departments. Recognized as employee of the month on multiple occasions for going above and beyond while caring for my residents and being a supporting role to coordinators. Provided assistive procedural services to Wellness Nurse and RN. Trained onboarding of new team members including shadowing

and skills demonstration. Provided supervisory support to designated care managers.

Private Household Nanny

August 2012 - June 2016 (3 years 11 months)

Glendale, California, United States

Supported children's emotional and social development by adapting communication tactics for differing child needs. Built stable, consistent and positive environment for 4 and 8-year-old child. Attended to before and after school needs of a boy and girl. Supervision of other household staff, such as housekeepers, private chefs, and other nannies. Additional duties included traveling with the family as needed, taking children to doctor's appointments, chauffeuring the children to lessons, and grocery shopping.

ABS Auto Auctions
Professional Sales Representative
April 2012 - October 2012 (7 months)
Norco, California, United States

Cold-called prospective customers to build relationship. Routinely checked in with clients to evaluate their satisfaction with service, resolve conflicts and provide information on new offerings. Landed new customer accounts through a consistent combination of perseverance, dedicated cold calling and exceptional service.

Education

West Coast University

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse \cdot (2018 - 2020)

Citrus College

Associate of Science - AS, Health Services/Allied Health/Health Sciences, General · (2011 - 2017)